Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS.128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Poetry Slams, 1991-1994
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - National Slam #6 1991, ID: 128.0668 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0668)
    - National Slam #7 1991, ID: 128.0669 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0669)
    - National Slam #8 1991, ID: 128.0670 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0670)
    - SF National Poetry Slam - Selects 9/93, 1993; ID: 128.0671 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0671)
    - SF National Poetry Slam 9/93, 1993; ID: 128.0672 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0672)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #1, ID: 128.0673 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0673)
      [Audio Only]
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #2, ID: 128.0674 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0674)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #3, ID: 128.0675 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0675)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #4, ID: 128.0676 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0676)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #5, ID: 128.0677 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0677)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #6, ID: 128.0678 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0678)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #7, ID: 128.0679 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0679)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #8, ID: 128.0680 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0680)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #1, 1993; ID: 128.0681 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0681)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #2, 1993; ID: 128.0682 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0682)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #3, 1993; ID: 128.0683 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0683)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 1], ID: 128.0684 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0684)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 2], ID: 128.0685 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0685)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 3], ID: 128.0686 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0686)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 4], ID: 128.0687 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0687)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 5], ID: 128.0688 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0688)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 6], ID: 128.0689 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0689)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 7], ID: 128.0690 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0690)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 8], ID: 128.0691 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0691)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 1], 1994; ID: 128.0692 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0692)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 2], 1994; ID: 128.0693 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0693)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 3], 1994; ID: 128.0694 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0694)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Backup #3], 1994; ID: 128.0695 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0695)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 4], 1994; ID: 128.0696 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0696)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 5], 1994; ID: 128.0697 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0697)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 6], 1994; ID: 128.0698 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0698)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 7], 1994; ID: 128.0699 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0699)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 8], 1994; ID: 128.0700 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0700)
- Series IX: Metro Home News, ca. 1991
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    Metro Home videos have not been preserved and may not be available for research.
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Interview w/ Bob Holman: Tape #1, [1991]; ID: 128.0701 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0701)
    - Interview w/ Bob Holman & Miguel Algarin: Tape #2, [1991]; ID: 128.0702 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0702)
    - Interview w/: Tape #3, [1991]; ID: 128.0703 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0703)
    - Interview w/ Miguel Algarin & Lois Griffith: Tape #4, [1991]; ID: 128.0704 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0704)
    - Interview w/ Lois Griffith: Tape #5, [1991]; ID: 128.0705 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0705)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café / Metro Home News: Tape #6, 1991; ID: 128.0706A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0706A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #10, [1991]; ID: 128.0707A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0707A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #11, [1991]; ID: 128.0708A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0708A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night (Sony) / Metro Home News: Tape #11A, [1991]; ID: 128.0709 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0709)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #12, [1991]; ID: 128.0710A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0710A)
    - Nuyorican / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #12A, [1991]; ID: 128.0711 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0711)
    - Nuyorican Café / Night / Metro Home News: Tape #13, [1991]; ID: 128.0712 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0712)
    - Nuyorican Poets / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #13A, [1991]; ID: 128.0713A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0713A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café / Night / Metro Home News: Tape #14, [1991]; ID: 128.0714 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0714)
    - Nuyorican Poet's / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #14A, [1991]; ID: 128.0715A (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0715A)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #1, [1991]; ID: 128.0716 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0716)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #2, [1991]; ID: 128.0717 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0717)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #3, [1991]; ID: 128.0718 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0718)
- Series X: Rise and Shine Productions, 1985-1995
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    Rise and Shine videos have not been preserved and may not be available for research.
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Unknown to the World, Undated; ID: 128.0719 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0719)
    - Left Over Tears, Undated; ID: 128.0720 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0720)
    - Gold Road to Lonliness, 1993; ID: 128.0721 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0721)
    - Just a Pair OF Eyes Moving, 1994; ID: 128.0722 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0722)
    - Boys & Girls, Undated; ID: 128.0723 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0723)
    - Girls & Boys, Undated; ID: 128.0724 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0724)
    - Outside, Inside Wishes, Undated; ID: 128.0725 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0725)
    - Feels of Dreams, Undated; ID: 128.0726 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0726)
    - Revolving Door, Undated; ID: 128.0727 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0727)
    - Power In Our Hands, 1989; ID: 128.0728 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0728)
    - My Soul Is, 1989; ID: 128.0729 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0729)
    - Change, 1994; ID: 128.0730 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0730)
    - Drugs Are Just A Big Lie, Undated; ID: 128.0731 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0731)
    - Home Poem, 1988; ID: 128.0732 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0732)
    - The Alien, Undated; ID: 128.0733 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0733)
    - Absence, Undated; ID: 128.0734 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0734)
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Video and Film, ca. 1995-1999
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    Miscellaneous videos have not been preserved and may not be available for research.
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Urbana, 2000; ID: 128.0735 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0735)
    - "Apollo Comedy Hour"; D. Knowledge's Stand-Up Performance, Undated; ID: 128.0736 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0736)
    - Sclactoff Funf, Undated; ID: 128.0737 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0737)
    - Millenium Show 2/26/2000, ID: 128.0738 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0738)
    - Gogel Bordello Live 2000, ID: 128.0739 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0739)
    - Passage: Quraysh Ali Lansang, Undated; ID: 128.0740 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0740)
    - The Bone Mama..., Undated; ID: 128.0741 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0741)
    - The ABCs of What I Hate, Undated; ID: 128.0742 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0742)
    - "City Arts" Show #103: "New York In Verse", 1995; ID: 128.0743 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0743)
    - The Real Deal, Undated; ID: 128.0744 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0744)
    - Bob Kaufman @ Vesuvio 3/76, 1976 (Taped); ID: 128.0745 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0745)
    - Spoken Word I + II, Undated; ID: 128.0746 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0746)
    - Planet Carava: Episode 1, Undated; ID: 128.0747 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0747)
    - At The Crossroads, 2000; ID: 128.0748 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0748)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, Undated; ID: 128.0749 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0749)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, Undated; ID: 128.0750 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0750)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, 1999; ID: 128.0751 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0751)
    - The Death of the Old Plymouth Rock Hen (Continuous Loop), 2000; ID: 128.0752 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0752)
    - St. Loius African Chorus, Undated; ID: 128.0753 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0753)
    - Fooling With Words Part 1, 2000 (Dub); ID: 128.0754 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0754)
    - Fooling With Words Part 2, 2000 (Dub); ID: 128.0755 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0755)
    - Fooling With Words Part 1, 1999 (Dub); ID: 128.0756 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0756)
    - Fooling With Words Part 2, 1999 (Dub); ID: 128.0757 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0757)
    - Poem Films by Steve Katz and Nikolai Katz, Undated; ID: 128.0758A (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0758A)
    - Hunting For Cherubs / DWJ, [1996]; ID: 128.0759A (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0759A)
    - USA Poetry, 1994; ID: 128.0760 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0760)
    - D. Di Prima: "Home Turf", 1991; ID: 128.0761 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0761)
    - "Intersection" At The Meeting Point of Music & Poetry - Rough Cut #3, 1996; ID: 128.0762 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0762)
    - Tama Mushi Iro: A Video of Bug Haiku by Issa, 1996; ID: 128.0763 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0763)
    - What He Should Learn From His Dream, 1999; ID: 128.0764 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0764)
    - Memories "96: Buck's Rock Camp, [1996]; ID: 128.0765 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0765)
    - Beccaria Cinema: Senales de Rota, Undated; ID: 128.0766 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0766)
    - Robert Bedoya, Bob Holman, Ricci: St. Marks 1/21/1987, ID: 128.0767 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0767)
    - [Dakota's] B-Day April 19, 1986, ID: 128.0768 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0768)
    - [Unknown], Undated; ID: 128.0769 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0769)
    - Horvaci Torvaki: Knitting Factory & Rehearsal, Undated; ID: 128.0770 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0770)
    - Reggie Gaines: "I Just Want To Catch A Cab!", Undated; ID: 128.0771 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0771)
    - N.Y. Hotline/ [Thouyser]: Korean Mkt. Protest!, [10/30/19??]; ID: 128.0772 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0772)
    - 6356#2, Undated; ID: 128.0773 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0773)
    - The World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout 2000: Sherman Alexie vs Bob Holman, ID: 128.0774 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0774)
    - Boys Will Be Boys, 1993; ID: 128.0775 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0775)
    - Saba, Undated; ID: 128.0776 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0776)
    - Carl Watson: "Eddy Paris", Undated; ID: 128.0777 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0777)
    - Jose Padua: NYC Marathon, 1992; ID: 128.0778 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0778)
    - R. Gaines: "CAB", Undated; ID: 128.0779 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0779)
    - SLAM: Bob Holman, Undated; ID: 128.0780 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0780)
    - Washington Square Films - Compilation Reel: Tape 5 of 7, 1993; ID: 128.0781 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0781)
    - Matt Cook, Undated; ID: 128.0782 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0782)
    - J: We Are The Majority, 1992; ID: 128.0783 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0783)
    - J.: "Keep the Promise", 1993; ID: 128.0784 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0784)
    - Eiléan Ni Chuilleanain & Nuala Ni Dhomhnaill, 1997; ID: 128.0785 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0785)
    - Yehuda Amichai, 1989; ID: 128.0786 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0786)
    - Robert Creeley, 1990; ID: 128.0787 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0787)
    - NVI Edit Black, 1991; ID: 128.0788 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0788)
    - [Unknown], Undated; ID: 128.0789 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0789)
    - New York In Verse, 1995; ID: 128.0790 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0790)
    - nycSLAMS, 2000; ID: 128.0791 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0791)
    - Bob Holman: Pass 2, Undated; ID: 128.0792 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0792)
    - Postmodern Pobre, 1992; ID: 128.0793 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0793)
    - Giovanni, Pound, Whitman, Williams, Undated; ID: 128.0794 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0794)
    - George D. Kovach: Kean College Forum, Undated; ID: 128.0795 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0795)
    - Sekou Sundiata: "Language of Life", Undated; ID: 128.0796 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0796)
    - Sekou Sundiata, Undated; ID: 128.0797 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0797)
    - Maggie Estep: "No More Mister Nice Guy" - CD Master Tape, 1994, ID: 128.0798A (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0798A)
    - Maggie Estep: "No More Mister Nice Guy" - 1997, ID: 128.0799A (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0799A)
    - Maggie Estep/ Poetry: Showbiz Today (CNN), 1994; ID: 128.0800 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0800)
    - Maggie Estep/ Poetry: Showbiz Today (CNN), 1994; ID: 128.0801 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0801)
    - Alterna Vision Vol. 42, Undated; ID: 128.0802A (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0802A)
    - Maggie Estep: R&R With Roger Rose, 1994; ID: 128.0803 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0803)
    - Hal Sirowitz: MTV's Spoken Word Unplugged April 1995, ID: 128.0804 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0804)
    - Allen Ginsberg on CNN Live & Larry King Live, 1996; ID: 128.0805 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0805)
    - Allen Ginsberg on New York 1 & MTV News, 1996; ID: 128.0806 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0806)
    - Slammin' (Trailer), Undated; ID: 128.0807 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0807)
    - Slammin', Undated; ID: 128.0808 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0808)
    - Haiku, Undated; ID: 128.0809 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0809)
      Format: 16 mm. Film
    - Poetry For Me!, Undated; ID: 128.0810 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0810)
- Series XII: Vinyl Sound Recordings
  Vinyl sound recordings have not been preserved and may not be available for research.
  - Subseries A: Vinyl Recordings - LPs, 12 in.
    - Sebastian Cabot, Actor, A Dramatic Reading With Music, Bob Dylan, Poet; MGM Records (Box 34)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - Greatest Rap Hits Volume 2; Sugar Hill Records (Box 34)
    - Boogie Down Productions, By All Means Necessary; Zomba Production Ltd. (Box 34)
    - You're the Guy I Want to Share My Money With, Laurie Anderson, John Giorno, William S. Burroughs; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Sugar, Alcohol, and Meat, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Sugar, Alcohol, and Meat, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Big Ego, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - John Giorno and Anne Waldman; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Yale Series of Recorded Poets, Louis MacNeice Reads From His Own Works; Decca Records (Box 34)
    - The Poetry of George Sefris Read in Greek by the Author and in English by the Translator Edmund Keeley; Caedmon Records (Box 34)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents The Tale of the Giant Rat of Sumatra; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Master Arts Series Allan Hodshire Presents Burke McHugh's Greenwich Village, USA, Unexpurgated Complete Edition; 20th Fox Record Corporation (Box 34)
    - Philadelphia International Records, Jocko; CBS Records (Box 34)
    - Joeski Love, Pee-wee's Dance; Vintertainment (Box 34)
    - Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew, Oh, My God!; Danya Records, Ltd. (Box 34)
    - UTFO, Full Force; Select Records (Box 34)
    - Sweet Soul Music; Enjoy Records (Box 34)
    - Ras Tefsa; Jafrica Records (Box 34)
    - Do You Like That Funky Beat (Ahh Beat, Beat) Kyle Brinson, Kool Kyle the Starchild and the Disco Dolls, Ronnie Ron and Crew; Enjoy Records (Box 34)
    - Congo; Nine Nine Records (Box 34)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 12 in.
    - Boogie Down Productions, Ghetto Music: The Blueprint of Hip Hop; Zomba Recording Corp. (Box 34)
    - Run-D.M.C, King of Rock; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 34)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Can Give You More/I Can't Live Without My Radio; Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Need a Beat/You'll Rock (Remix); Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - Triple Threat by Z-3 MCs; Beauty and the Beat Records (Box 34)
    - Cameo Word Up; Polygram Records (Box 34)
    - Party Time, Dimples D.; Streetwise Records (Box 34)
    - Run-D.M.C.; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 34)
    - Roxanne (with UTFO); Select Records (Box 34)
    - Roxanne Shante; Pop Art Records (Box 34)
    - Malcolm X: Music by Keith LeBlanc; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Afrika Bambaataa and the Jazzy 5/ The Kryptic Krew featuring Tina B: Jazzy Sensation; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Greatest Beats; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Afrika Bambaata and the Soul Sonic Force: Planet Rock; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - The Firesign Theatre: Don't Crush That Dwarf, Hand me the Pliers; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Proctor and Bergman: TV or Not TV; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Firesign Theatre Sez Everything You Know is Wrong; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - The Black Flames/ b/w The Public Enemy: from the original Soundtrack of the Tewntieth Century Fox Film Less Than Zero; Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - LL Cool J, I Need a Beat; Def Jam Recordings (Box 35)
    - Sun City, Artists United Against Apartheid; Manhattan Records (Box 35)
    - LL Cool J, Rock the Bells; Def Jam Recordings (Box 35)
    - Shinehead: Chain Gang-Rap; Elektra/ Asylum Records (Box 35)
    - Fast Money; Star Maker Records (Box 35)
    - Disco 45: Rapper's Delight; Joe Gibbs Music Corp. (Box 35)
    - Firesign Theatre Predicts in the Next World You're on Your Own; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: "Fighting Clowns;" Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents Waiting for the Electrician or Someone Like Him; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Lawyer's Hospital; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Comedy of Proctor and Bergman: Give Us a Break; Mercury (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: I Think We're All Bozos on This Bus; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - David Ossman's How Time Flys: A Hi-Fi Sci-Fi Comedy Starring The Firesign Theatre; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - Roxanne (Fly) Shante Featuring Steady "B": I'm Fly Shante; Pop Art Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: Not Insane; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents Nick Danger, Third Eye: The Case of the Missing Shoe; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents "Fighting Clowns," With Special Limited Edition 7" Picture Disc; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - Spike Jones, The Craziest Show on Earth; M.F. Distribution Co., Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Conception Corporation Presents Conceptionland and Other States of Mind; Cotillion (Box 35)
    - Bob Newhart, The Button-Down Man Strikes Back!; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Best of Stan Fredberg; Capitol Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - National Lampoon Radio Dinner; Banana Records (Box 35)
    - The Marx Bros.: The Original Voice Tracks from Their Greatest Movies; Decca Records (Box 35)
    - William E. McEuen Presents Steve Martin: "Let's Get Small;" Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - Movies are Better Than Ever, Jonathan Winters; Verve Records (Box 35)
    - W.C. Fields and Mae West; Proscenium Records (Box 35)
    - Dear Friends: The Firesign Theatre; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - An Anthology of French Poetry Volume Two: From Pierre Corneille to Charles Baudelaire, Poems Selected and Arranged by Georges Guy; Period Records (Box 35)
    - An Anthology of French Poetry Volume One: From Charles D'Orleans to Tristan L'Hermite, Poems Selected and Arranged by Georges Guy; Period Records (Box 35)
    - Understanding and Appreciation of Poetry, Prepared by Morris Schreiber; Folkways Records (Box 35)
    - Metaphysical and Love Lyrics of the Seventeenth Century, a Reading by Sir Cedric Hardwicke and Robert Newton Directed by Howard O. Sackler; Caedmon Records (Box 35)
    - Bonzo Goes to Washington: 5 Minutes; Sleeping Bag Records (Box 35)
    - Just Another Asshole #5, edited by Barbara Ess and Glenn Branca; JAA (Box 35)
    - Liverpool Scene: Bread on the Night; RCA Records (Box 35)
    - Jill Kroesen, Stop Vicious Cycles; Lovely Music (Box 35)
    - Laurie Anderson, Big Science; Warner Bros. Records (Box 35)
    - Laurie Anderson: O Superman/ Walk the Dog; Warner Bros. Records (Box 35)
    - Bonzo Dog Doo/Dah Band, Gorilla; Imperial Records (Box 36)
    - Bonzo Dog Band, Let's Make Up and be Friendly; United Artists Records (Box 36)
    - Laurie Anderson, Mister Heartbreak; Waner Bros. Records (Box 36)
    - State of the Union; Zoar Records (Box 36)
    - State of the Union; Zoar Records (Box 36)
    - The Jim Carroll Band, Dry Dreams; ATCO Records (Box 36)
    - Falco, Rock Me Amadeus, the American Edit; A and M Records (Box 36)
    - Duck's Breath Mystery Theatre, Born to be Tiled; Rounder Records (Box 36)
    - Roger Ruskin Spear, Electric Shocks; United Artists Records (Box 36)
    - Bongos Bass and Bob; [Penn Jillette] (Box 36)
    - Karen Finley, Tales of Taboo; Pow Wow Art International (Box 36)
    - Songs of Leonard Cohen; CBS Records (Box 36)
    - Leonard Cohen, Songs From a Room; CBS Records (Box 36)
    - Medieval Romance Poetry, A Survey of Medieval Romance Literatures by Dr. Mario Pei; Folkways Records (Box 36)
    - United States Presidents' Series, Actual Speeches of Franklin D. Roosevelt and John F. Kennedy; Library in Sound Records (Box 36)
    - Marilyn Monroe, The Complete Recordings; Recording Arts Reference Edition (Box 36)
    - Bob Rosenthal, Poetry Project Test Pressings; RGH Record Manufacturing Corp. [Two LPs] (Box 36)
    - Poetry Olympics Volume 1; All Round Records (Box 36)
    - Terry Garthwaite, Bobbie Louise Hawkins, Rosalie Sorrels, Live at the Great American Music Hall; Flying Fish Records (Box 36)
    - The World Record, Readings at the St. Mark's Poetry Project 1969-1980; The Poetry Project (Box 36)
    - Morrison St., A Spoken Word Anthology; Paris Records (Box 36)
    - Meredith Monk/Dolmen Music; ECM Records (Box 36)
    - Ben Bagley Presents Kenward Elmslie in Palais Bimbo Lounge Show; Painted Smiles Records (Box 36)
    - Mao Tse-Tung: Quotations From the Chairman Read by Martin Donegan; Peerless Records (Box 36)
    - Chile: Songs for the Resistance; Paredon Records (Box 36)
    - We Shall Overcome, Songs of the "Freedom Riders" and the "Sit-Ins;" Folkway Records (Box 36)
    - Test Pressing, Version 1, Volume 1; Tartown Record Co. (Box 36)
    - Roxanne Shante Def Mix Volume 1; Pop Art Records (Box 36)
    - RZA Presents Wu-Tang Killa Bees, The Swarm Volume 1; Wu-Tang Records, Inc. (Box 36)
    - He's the D.J., I'm the Rapper, D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince; Jive Records (Box 36)
    - Roxanne Shante, Roxanne's Revenge; Pop Art Records (Box 36)
    - Run-D.M.C.; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 36)
    - Newcleus, Jam on It; Sunnyview Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew; Reality Records (Box 37)
    - Beastie Boys: Cooky Puss, Bonus Batter, Beastie Revolution; Ratcage Mir (Box 37)
    - Kurtis Blow: Tough; Mercury (Box 37)
    - Just Ice; Fresh Records (Box 37)
    - Grandmixer DST Crazy Cuts; Island Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - L.L. Cool J, Radio; Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Sutra Single, Disco 3; Sutra Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Need a Beat/You'll Rock (Remix); Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Martin Luther, Hurt 'Em Bad and the S.C. Band; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince Rock the House; Jive (Box 37)
    - Count Coolout, Rhythm Rap Rock; WMOT Records (Box 37)
    - Beastie Boys, Licensed to Ill; Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Ice Cube, AmeriKKKa's Most Wanted; Priority Records (Box 37)
    - Krush Groove, Music from the Original Motion Picture Sound Track; Warner Bros. Records (Box 37)
    - Wild Style; Animal Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Funky 4+1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Vocal, Funky 4 Plus 1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Vocal, Funky 4 Plus 1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Freedom, Grandmaster Flash and the Furious 5; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Kurtis Blow, "The Breaks;" Mercury (Box 37)